http://www.iaspei.org/documents/privacy-policy

Commission on Education and Outreach
Commission on Seismological Observation and Interpretation (CoSOI)
Commission on Tectonophysics and Crustal Structure
Commission on Earthquake Generation Process - Physics, Modelling, and Monitoring for Forecast
Commission on Earth Structure and Geodynamics
Commission on Earthquake Hazard, Risk and Strong Ground Motion
Commission on Earthquake Source Mechanics
Asian Seismological Commission
European Seismological Commission
Africa Seismological Commission (AfSC)
IASPEI Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to the International Association of Seismology and Physics of the Earth’s (IASPEI). This Privacy Policy explains what data we may collect from you and how we may use, store, and transfer your information. We may make changes to this Privacy Policy. If we do, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on the IASPEI website so that you will always know what information we collect and how it might be used. This Privacy Policy was last modified on 09 January 2019.
Who we are
International Association of Seismology and Physics of the Earth’s (IASPEI)
c/o NORSAR
Gunnar Randers vei
PO Box 53, N-2007 Kjeller
Norway
Phone: +47 41614946
iaspei@norsar.no
What personal information the IASPEI collects about you
When you interact with the IASPEI e.g., by taking a role within IASPEI or within one of its sub-entities (incl., Regional and Thematic Commissions, Working Groups, Committees etc.), or by signing up to receive e-mails through the mailing list, IASPEI receives and collects personal information about you. This personal information may include first name, surname, title, role within IASPEI, physical (work) address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address.
How the IASPEI uses personal information
The IASPEI uses the information we receive from our sub-entities and collect about you to stay in contact with the IASPEI community; to be able to inform you about important announcements, events, and other relevant news; to provide you with information that you have requested; or to communicate relevant information about IASPEI projects, data, services, and other updates. Depending on your role within IASPEI or within one of its sub-entities, this personal information might be published on the IASPEI website or in the IASPEI Newsletter subject to your consent. We keep your information for no longer than is necessary for the purposes it was collected for.
Updating or deleting your personal information
The accuracy of your personal information is important to the IASPEI. You can modify or delete your personal information incl. updating your subscription to the IASPEI Newsletter by contacting the IASPEI Secretary General (iaspei@norsar.no). Requests to unsubscribe may not take effect immediately.
Protecting personal information
The IASPEI uses safeguards to ensure that your personal information is secure. Once we have received your information, we will use appropriate procedures and security features intended to prevent unauthorized access to our database.
Requesting removal of content from IUGG online resources
You have a right to your privacy. We would like to assure that we address your privacy concerns. If you identify any content you desire to be removed, please contact the IASPEI Secretary General (iaspei@norsar.no). You can file a complaint about how we process your personal information by contacting the IASPEI Secretary General (iaspei@norsar.no).
Contact | Privacy Policy | © 2020 by IASPEI. All rights reserved. | Powered by: International Seismological Centre (ISC) and Grav
Commission on Seismological Observation and Interpretation (CoSOI)
Commission on Tectonophysics and Crustal Structure
Commission on Earthquake Generation Process - Physics, Modelling, and Monitoring for Forecast
Commission on Earth Structure and Geodynamics
Commission on Earthquake Hazard, Risk and Strong Ground Motion
Commission on Earthquake Source Mechanics
Asian Seismological Commission
European Seismological Commission
Africa Seismological Commission (AfSC)
